unfriendtracker.com 2015-10-29

# Privacy Policy

UnfriendTracker's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using UnfriendTracker, located at www.unfriendtracker.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "UnfriendTracker" or "Website"). By using or accessing UnfriendTracker, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

1\. The Information We Collect

When you visit UnfriendTracker you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site. 

When you register with UnfriendTracker, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your email address, favorite social networks, and names of friends who are on those social networks. 

When you enter UnfriendTracker, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all UnfriendTracker visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that makes it easier for you to login when you come back to UnfriendTracker. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature or you can choose not to automatically login to the site. 

When you use UnfriendTracker, you may set up your account, add favorite social networks, and add your friends on those networks in order to track your friends list changes over time. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view the changes in your data over time. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. 

You post User Submissions (as defined in the UnfriendTracker Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Submissions you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on UnfriendTracker is a violation of the UnfriendTracker Terms of Service and should be reported. If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and may send reminders to them. UnfriendTracker stores this information to send invitations and reminders, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, to allow you to see invitations you have sent, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database. 

UnfriendTracker may also collect information about you from other sources, such as other users of the UnfriendTracker service through the operation of the service in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. 

By using UnfriendTracker, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States. 

2\. Children Under Age 18

UnfriendTracker does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for UnfriendTracker or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to or on UnfriendTracker. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us through the form on our contact page. 

3\. Children Under the Age of 18

We recommend that minors 18 years of age or younger ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves or their friends to anyone over the Internet. 

4\. Use of Information Obtained by UnfriendTracker

When you register with UnfriendTracker, you create your own user account and add whichever social networks that you wish. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by UnfriendTracker that we think you may find valuable. 

UnfriendTracker may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. UnfriendTracker reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications. 

UnfriendTracker may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. This information is used in aggregate in order to allow for the planning of ad campaigns or merely for statistical purposes. 

5\. Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Any information that you post to your account will not be viewable to other Users. 

We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about UnfriendTracker, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the UnfriendTracker-specified purposes. UnfriendTracker may provide your personal information to third parties with whom they have a business relationship for the purposes of securing the services and products you have requested or provide you with additional marketing materials from which you may choose additional products or services. UnfriendTracker may make your personal information available to companies or other entities not affiliated with the UnfriendTracker that have goods, services and offers that might be of interest to you so that they may send you these offers or present them to you. 

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the UnfriendTracker service or using the UnfriendTracker name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the UnfriendTracker business, or individual business units owned by UnfriendTracker, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. UnfriendTracker further reserves the right to disclose, transfer or sell your personal information to companies who are affiliated with UnfriendTracker in UnfriendTracker's sole discretion. If UnfriendTracker changes ownership through an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of business status, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the right to use your personal information collected. 

6\. Links

UnfriendTracker may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by UnfriendTracker. 

7\. Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on UnfriendTracker are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. UnfriendTracker does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on UnfriendTracker unless you choose to share it with them. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by UnfriendTracker and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. 

8\. Changing or Removing Information

Most User Submissions are not editable once submitted, but can be updated. Most User Submissions on a user account can be changed or deleted by contacting customer service or using the UI. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time. 

9\. Security

UnfriendTracker takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email is not recognized as a secure form of communication, we request that you not send private information to us by email. If you have any questions about the security of UnfriendTracker Web Site, please contact us via the contact page. 

10\. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of UnfriendTracker, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please visit our contact page. You may also contact us by mail at 5400 Glenridge Drive, #420813, Atlanta, Ga. 30342.
